{
  "stocks": {
    "0": {
      "question": "What are some factors that cause the stock price to fluctuate?",
      "answers": {
        "0": "Me, me, and me!",
        "1": "A company’s public image, product quality, and product demand.",
        "2": "What are you saying? Stocks don’t fluctuate."
      },
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "Stock price is governed by supply and demand. The demand for a stock can be influenced by the company’s public image, product quality, and product demand."
    },
    "1": {
      "question": "Does a stock price go up if people don’t like the company?",
      "answers": {
        "0": "No.",
        "1": "Yes.",
        "2": "Most likely yes."
      },
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation":"It will not go up."
    },
    "2": {
      "question": "Can I invest in the stock market?",
      "answers": {
        "0": "Only if you are over the age of 40.",
        "1": "Only if you are rich.",
        "2": "Anyone can invest in the stock market."
      },
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation":"Anyone can invest in the stock market!"
    },
    "3": {
      "question": "When should you start investing in the stock market?",
      "answers": {
        "0": "As early as possible.",
        "1": "When I am 45.",
        "2": "Whenever I feel like getting quick money."
      },
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation":"The earlier you start, the better."
    }
  },
  "finance": {
    "0": {
      "question": "What is a loan?",
      "answers": {
        "0": "A loan is a binding agreement between a lender and a borrower that ensures that the borrower will pay back the lender.",
        "1": "It is a document that you turn in to your teacher.",
        "2": "A legal document that can be submitted in place of a passport."
      },
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "Honestly come on."
    },
    "1": {
      "question": "Are there times when it is good to take out a loan?",
      "answers": {
        "0": "Yes.",
        "1": "No.",
        "2": "Why am I here?"
      },
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "There are times when a loan might be beneficial to take out."
    },
    "2": {
      "question": "Should I take out a loan?",
      "answers": {
        "0": "NO!",
        "1": "Yes!",
        "2": "Maybe- It depends on your circumstances."
      },
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "Whether you should take out a loan depends on your financial circumstances and your goals."
    },
    "3": {
      "question": "Would taking out a loan for a new house be smart?",
      "answers": {
        "0": "Of course not.",
        "1": "It usually is.",
        "2": "Why are you buying a house?"
      },
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "This is often a good idea because a house is one of the most expensive purchases a person can make, and one may not have enough money to pay for it in full. The value of a house also tends to increase over time!"
    }
  },
  "habits": {
    "0": {
      "question": "What does it mean to spend wisely?",
      "answers": {
        "0": "Spending wisely means that you have a plan that you follow to make sure you don’t overspend.",
        "1": "It means that you spend as much as you want on anything.",
        "2": "It means that you spend nothing, ever."
      },
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "Spending as much as you want on anything is not a smart strategy and will cause you to be in a ton of debt. On the other hand, spending wisely doesn’t mean you spend nothing. It means that you don’t buy everything you want."
    },
    "1": {
      "question": "Why should you spend wisely?",
      "answers": {
        "0": "Because why not?",
        "1": "So that you can manage your expenses and not go into debt.",
        "2": "So that you can show off your mad skills."
      },
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "Although I'm sure you have mad skills and don't need a reason to spend wisely, the real reason to spend wisely is to manage your expenses and not go into debt."
    },
    "2": {
      "question": "What is one tactic for spending wisely?",
      "answers": {
        "0": "Don’t go to stores.",
        "1": "Sit at home and eat nothing.",
        "2": "Set a limit on your credit card."
      },
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "That's unrealistic. Setting a limit on your credit card, on the other hand, can help you manage your finances."
    },
    "3": {
      "question": "What is budgeting?",
      "answers": {
        "0": "Budgeting is making sure that you divide your income properly.",
        "1": "It is spending way to little on needs and too much on wants.",
        "2": "It is creating a schedule to buy your groceries."
      },
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "Budgeting is dividing your income properly."
    }
  }
}